joy in place of sorrow.
He who from you became incarnate,
God and man has directed to life
him who fell from it.
Hallelujah, hallelujah,
glory to you, O God.
hallelujah, glory to you, O God.
Hallelujah, hallelujah,
Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
Vox as ioth eos
Again and again in peace
Let us pray to the Lord
Lord have mercy
Help us, save us, have mercy on us
And protect us, O God, by your grace
Lord, have mercy.
Remembering our all-holy, immaculate, most blessed
and glorious Lady the Theotokos
and ever-Virgin Mary,
with all the saints, let us commend ourselves
and one another
and our whole life to Christ our God.
For blessed is your name and glorified is your kingdom.
Have mercy.
For travelers by land, sea and air,
for the sick, the suffering,
the captives, and for their salvation,
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For our deliverance from all affliction,
wrath, danger, and distress,
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, I am.
Help us, save us, have mercy on us, and protect us, O God, by your grace.
Lord, have mercy.
Remembering our most holy, pure, blessed, and glorious Lady the Theotokos,
and ever-Virgin Mary with all the same.
Let us commit ourselves and one another
and our whole life to Christ our God.
To you, O Lord.
For to you belong all glory, honor, and worship
to the Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit
now and forever and to the ages of ages.
on the cross, Jesus' death on the cross, that he was able to destroy death for us.
And through his death, resurrection, and promises resurrection to all of us.
The Holy Cross sits on the altar every day throughout the year. And there are just three
occasions during the church year that it is brought out in the midst of the people,
so that they may take courage and strength, that they may continue.
the rigors of the fast. Then last Sunday we commemorated St. John of the Ladder,
who wrote this beautiful work, The Ladder of Divine Ascent, of which Father Michael spoke
so beautifully last Sunday. He likened St. John of the Ladder, likened this journey through life
as really like climbing a ladder,
and every rung on the ladder is a...
a vice that needs to be overcome,
and a virtue to be attained.
30 rungs.
And once we get to the top,
we'll experience what the church knows as theoses.
That is, vision of God.
Vision of God.
As Jesus said in the Beatitudes,
blessed are the pure in heart,
for they shall see.
with the fear of God, with faith, and with love drawn near.
Ong de Paraná,
Thank you.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE